wittyandpretty.com 2013-05-06

# Privacy Policy | Witty & Pretty

**Introduction**

Action Factory strongly believes that your personal information deserves protection. By using our website you consent and agree to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information and to the privacy practices set out in this policy. We expressly reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time.

This privacy policy is intended to inform you of the collection, use and disclosure of information that we collect. All references to “we,” “us” and “our” are intended to mean Action Factory, and all references to “you” and “your” are intended to mean users who have been exposed to our services. “Partner Sites” refer to advertiser and publisher websites that use our services. Because our Privacy Policy may be updated periodically, we encourage you to review these Action Factory pages on a regular basis.

**Our Services**

At Action Factory, we collect certain anonymous and non-personally identifiable information about users in order to display effective advertisements. Based on the behavior and preferences of the users that we have identified, we seek to group those users into certain categories. We then seek to display the most relevant advertisements to the users in those categories.

### **The Anonymous Data**

**Anonymous Data**

The Anonymous Data that we collect about users through our services is anonymous, non-personally identifiable information and may include such information as your Internet Protocol address, your browser, recent search history, and your activity on the websites of our partners (the “Anonymous Data”). (An Internet Protocol (“IP”) address is an address on the internet that is automatically assigned to your computer when you establish a connection on the Internet.)

**Personally Identifiable Information**

We do collect certain personally identifiable information if you register with us on our website. This personally identifiable information, which may include your name, company information, address, and your website information (collectively, “PII”), is only captured when you register on our site. This PII is not shared, sold or rented to any other third parties. If you would like to have this PII changed, you can contact us at the email below.

**How We Collect the Anonymous Data**

We may collect this Anonymous Data, directly or indirectly, from our network of Partner Sites, or we may purchase this Anonymous Data from other third party providers.

For Anonymous Data that we purchase from third party providers, the Privacy Policy for such third party providers applies to the provisioning of that Anonymous Data. The use of that Anonymous Data by Action Factory, however, is governed by this Policy.

For Anonymous Data that we collect, directly or indirectly, we typically employ the use of “pixel tags” and/or “cookies.” Pixel tags are small bits of code that provide a method of delivery information on a webpage which allow the operator of the page or a third party to collect information about the users of the page. Cookies are small text files that are stored on the browser of your computer that uniquely identify your browser and provide information to the cookie sender. Many websites send cookies to the browsers that are visiting those sites, and many browsers are initially configured to accept cookies. You may be able to change your browser settings to refuse cookies or to alert you of when a cookie has been placed on your browser. Check your browser for details.

**Use of Anonymous Data**

We use the Anonymous Data that we collect in order to display advertisements that we believe may be relevant to you. In seeking to identify relevant advertisements, we use this Anonymous Data to create and refine user segments, develop and refine algorithms, and to understand better how your interaction with a website might be of interest to advertisers. We do not link any Anonymous Data to the PII collected on our website.

Further, we may share aggregated information that we have learned from the use of the Anonymous Data with third parties. Such information may include traffic patterns, sales, and other site information. For example, we might share statistics on how many customers viewed or clicked on a particular advertisement.

We belong to ad networks that use your browsing history across websites to choose which ads to display on their sites. To learn more, and to opt out of seeing interest-based advertisements on these sites, visit the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) home page. Websites may also offer their own opt-out methods for interest-based advertising.

We do not sell the Anonymous Data to third parties.

**Blogs and Testimonials**

Please note that if you use a blog on our site, you should be aware that anything you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. As a result, we are not responsible for the PII you choose to submit in these forums. Some of our clients have chosen to post testimonials on our site. We have obtained the approvals of such clients to post their PII along with the testimonial.

Please note that we have a third party cookie, Google Sitemap, on our site which assists us with the operation, maintenance and analytics of the website.

**Anonymous Data Security**

We employ reasonable industry standard measures to protect against the unauthorized access, disclosure, modification or destruction of the Anonymous Data. While we are committed to ensuring the security of the Anonymous Data, you should be aware that no Anonymous Data protection measures can provide 100% guarantee of security. Consequently, we do not warrant or guarantee the security of the Anonymous Data.

**Anonymous Data Retention**

Action Factory does not use or retain any personally identifiable information (PII) and only relies upon non-PII. Action Factory shall maintain such data only for as long as necessary for practical business purposes, unless required to do otherwise by law.

**Changes to Action Factory  Corporate Structure**

If all or part of Action Factory is sold, merged, or otherwise transferred to another entity, the Anonymous Data and PII gathered by Action Factory may be transferred as part of that transaction. Action Factory will take reasonable measures to ensure that such Anonymous Data is used in a manner consistent with the Privacy Policy under which it was collected. If such a change in Action Factory’s corporate structure occurs, you will be notified as described below in the section entitled “Your Consent and Right to Change this Policy.”

**Disclosure**

The above notwithstanding, we may disclose any of the Anonymous Data, any PII or any other information we collect when we believe that we have a legal obligation to do so. For example, we may disclose any of the above in order to (i) protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served or (ii) protect or defend our proprietary rights.

**Disclaimer**

We have no control over, nor any responsibility for, the privacy policies and/or content of any of our Partner Sites. As a result, we disclaim any and all responsibility for, or affiliation with, any third party cookies, pixels or practices.

**Your Consent & Right to Change This Policy**

By visiting our website (shortsalesecrets.co) and/or the website of any of our partners, you hereby consent to our collection, storage, and dissemination of your Anonymous Data as described above. If we decide to change our privacy policy materially, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of such changes. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.

**Effective Date and Governing Law**

This policy was updated on March 25, 2013. This Privacy Policy and any matter relating to this Web Site, shall be governed by the laws of California. If any part of this agreement is deemed to be invalid, illegal or unenforceable, then the invalid or unenforceable part shall be removed without affecting the legality, validity and enforceability of the remainder of this Privacy Policy. Further, the illegal, invalid or unenforceable provision removed shall be replaced by a legal, valid, enforceable provision that most closely reflects the original intent of the original provision.
